[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much did the USA pay Russia for Alaska?", "correct_answer": "$7.2 million", "incorrect_answers": ["$72 million", "$720 million", "$720,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what group of dog breeds does the Beagle dog breed belong?", "correct_answer": "Hound group", "incorrect_answers": ["Terrier group", "Toy group", "Herding group"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress plays Claire Redfield in Resident Evil: Extinction?", "correct_answer": "Ali Larter", "incorrect_answers": ["Ashanti", "Spencer Locke", "Milla Jovovich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The lines Wildcats everywhere, raise your hands up in the air are from the song Were All in This Together.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which group recorded the hit single Sugar Daddy in 1971?", "correct_answer": "Jackson 5", "incorrect_answers": ["Bread", "Journey", "The Mamas and the Papas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The town of Juarez, Mexico is located next to what U.S. city?", "correct_answer": "El Paso, TX", "incorrect_answers": ["San Diego, CA", "Laredo, TX", "Sierra Vista, AZ"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An important supplement for pregnant women, what is vitamin B9 more commonly known as?", "correct_answer": "Folic Acid", "incorrect_answers": ["Thiamine", "Riboflavin", "Niacin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did the US government buy for the Native Alaskans in 1891?", "correct_answer": "The basis of their caribou herd", "incorrect_answers": ["Motorized sleds", "A fire truck", "Ice boxes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the smallest extant species of crocodilian on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Musky Caiman", "incorrect_answers": ["Smooth-fronted Caiman", "Spectacled Caiman", "Yacare Caiman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed U.S. President Richard Nixon in Oliver Stones 1995 movie Nixon?", "correct_answer": "Anthony Hopkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Nicholson", "None of these", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are aardvarks an endangered species?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Bruce Waynes mother?", "correct_answer": "Martha Wayne", "incorrect_answers": ["Terri Wayne", "Janet Wayne", "Samantha Wayne"]}]